In a town of suspects, one man stands accused.
Murder at Yellowstone City is a western, mystery film directed by Richard Gray.
A former slave who arrives in Yellowstone City, Montana, a desolate former
boomtown now on the decline, looking for a place to call home.
On that same day, a local prospector discovers gold - and is murdered.
Sheriff Ambrose, played by Gabriel Byrne.
Thaddeus, played by Thomas Jane.
Cicero, played by Isaiah Mustafa.
Alice, played by Anna Camp.
Young Jim, played by Nat Wolff.
Edgar, played by Richard Dreyfuss.
Murder at Yellowstone City (formerly titled Murder at Emigrant Gulch) is an American
Western film directed by Richard Gray from a screenplay by Eric Belgau.
The tone is mind_bending.